ERHAN YAYLALI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Odense, Denmark
+(45) 50 23 19 14
erhanyaylali9@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/erhanyaylali
github.com/erhanyaylali1
https://yaylali.net/

EDUCATION

Istanbul Technical University, Istanbul

Computer Engineering 2016 - 2021

SKILLS

- · Javascript, JQuery
- · React, Redux
- Next JS
- · CSS and SCSS
- · Razor Pages (.cshtml)
- · Google Console
- Figma

LANGUAGES

- Turkish Native Speaker
- · English C1 Level
- · Danish Al Level

SUMMARY

I am frontend developer who has more than 3 years experience on the field. As a person, I am good at collabrating, working as a team and I am very open minded person. Beside developing websites, I had experience on working with UI/UX team for design, handling SEO optimization and communication with costumers.

EXPERIENCES

Hesehus A/S, Odense, Denmark
Front End Developer | 07.2022 - Present

- My responsibilities were developing the pages, maintaining good SEO results, working with UI/UX and being in communication with customers.
- Some technologies I was using in solutions were React, Next JS, SCSS, JQuery, Razor Pages

Yapı Kredi Techonology, Istanbul, Turkey Fullstack Developer | 06.2021 - 07.2022

- My team was developing a website for lawyers and law firms.
- My responsibility was creating endpoints on backend, creating and designing new pages with React and collaborating with other teams.

Exhibin, Istanbul, Turkey

Frontend Developer | 09.2020 - 12.2020

 I was working developing pages in Exhibin using React and SCSS as student worker

Ibtech, Gebze, Turkey

Web Developer Intern | 02.2021 - 06.2021

IBM Turkey, Istanbul, Turkey

Al Cloud Intern | 07.2020 - 08.2020